Inventory of the Gordon Leo McDonough papers 0366
USC Libraries Special Collections
- File of COMMITTEES
  - File of COMMITTEES, 1950-54
    - Food Investigation H RES 323 Public Law 360 (a.o. investigate chemical in foods, Fedreal Meat Inspection Act,legislation proposed by FDA, report on H RES 323, Toxicity tests packaging material, condensed list of chemical in foods), 1950-51
    - Food 82 Congress H R 447 H RES 74 323 (Investigation in use of chemicals in foods, Union Calendar 1139, F D A, 1950, '51
    - Food H R 323 329 4277 4901 5740 2341 447 74 (booklets: use of chemicals in food, gauging toxicity of chemicals in foods), Jan 1952-'55
    - Food (reportson soil, insecticides etc. -listing at [UNK]
    - Public Works, General, 1950-51
    - Public Works, Beach Erosion (Public Law 166 520 727 (Beach erosion control Report of State of California, Point [UNK] Pedro), 1951
    - Public Works, Flood Control Public Law 534 (Review of Federal reprts, Colorado River Storage Project), 195-'52
    - Public Works Public Buildings, 1951
    - Public Works Public Roads H R 159 6180 6094 7340 S 2365 2363 2437 2585, 1950-'52
    - Public Works Rivers Harbors HJR 337 HR 1555 2752 (analyses of power aspects of St Lauwrence Seaway Project '51), 1950-'52
  - File of COMMITTEES, 1952-1960
    Arr. aphabetically by subject of committees in folders
    - Agriculture, 1957 (Box Box COMM. 38)
    - Air pollution Manufacturing, 1957
    - Bank Currency, General H R 4090 5667, 1953 1953
    - Bank Currency Housing HR 5827 6694 Private Law 87-229 S 1501 1800 2126 (Insurance funds, FHA analyses mortgages/general information housing authoritority city L A/Public Law 345/Wherry Housing Ass.), 1955, '56
    - Bank Currency, Housing HR 2938 7839 Public Law 171 (housing act of 1954/minority group housing-racial -/police costs/questions answers/Richmond proposal, amend 1954 Housing act, 1953, '54
    - Bank Currency Housing H R 2424 2669 6659 10637 12752 13107 HJR 556 S 4035 H RES 203 (Chicago Housing Authority 1955-relocations/Chicago Housing bill/cooperative housing FHA 213/housing authority county of L A/mortgage warehousing/swimming pool legislation/ urban renewal program/urban renewal insurance program FHA 220 221, 1957
    - Banking Currency Commerce HR 6230 7893 12 1728 S 975, 1952-54
      (international bank for reconstruction developpent)
    - Banking Currency Commerce HR 12 2674 5144 5710 6055 6227 7071 8555 11510 S 256 972 1187 1188 1189 1936 S 880 2674, 1955-56
      (Expansion of bank holdings companies/housing home finance agency)
    - Banking Currency Commerce HR 7026 S 1451 3651 3497 (Bank holding campany act/community facilities act '58/small business investment act '58), 1952-58
    - Banking Commerce Price, wages rents Hr 430 1603 17282, 1953
    - Committee on Government operations HR 4406 HJRES 300 (converting dry- (cargo vessels/commission for aeronautics Cleveland/Fallbrook case/labor union welfare funds/naval paint factories/orgination of executive branch of gernment/public accountants subcommittee/reorganisation of US dept. of agriculture/refrigeration ships/bureau of engravingprinting, Lewis flight propulsion lab, 1953, '54
    - Bank Currency Savings loan, 1954
    - Housing sub-committee H RES 86 (Housinghome finance agency/shreveport/Bossier), 1957
    - Shipbuilding, 1957
    - Space (NASA), 1959-60
    - Water, Flood Forest Fires control (reports 1955 '56 Dept. of Interior Saline Water Conversion), 1957
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDANCE G C I, 1945-'56
    Arranged alphabetically by subject headersi in folders C thr. T
    - California delegation committee on employment problems affectin the West Coast (Box 39)
    - General A, 1954-'56
    - Genral B, Mc Carran- Wather Act H R 6227 S 2577 Immigration, 1955-'56
    - General C, H R 6376 Alaska Mental, Health HR 11223 May Williams Show pamphet Polio, 1954-'56
    - General D, Freud Einstein as deceivers in Science, 1955-'56 1956
    - General E F G, Fed. Civil Defense Adm.: Home protection Excercises '54, 1955-'56
    - General H, 1955-'56
    - General I J K L, 1955-'56
    - General M P Q H R 7226, 1955-'56
    - General S, 1947-'48
    - General T, A B 2307, 1947-'48
    - General U, 1947-'48
    - General V, 1947-'48
    - General W, (merit presentation Jack Warner), 1947-'48
    - General W a, 1947-'48
    - General X Y Z, 1947-'48
    - General L, Program to rduce Fed. dominiation over state local affairs, 1951-'54 1954
    - Letters answered, 1956
    - Miscelleneous correspondance H J Res546, 1946
    - Publications received (cut flowers production markets, Oct 1947 1946)
    - Publications Receaived, 1947-'48
    - Publications requested, general
    - Publications requested, service men Public Law 346
    - Publications sent- American legion
    - Publications sens-miscelleneous, 1945
    - Request for personal recommendations
    - Request for notification bill passage, 1946
    - Special thanks for books, publications
    - Thanks letters H R 5059
    - Thanks H R 4654 5059, 1946-'47
    - Thanks, May 1947
    - Thanks, Jan-1948
    - Thanks Public Law 759 775 810, 1948-'49
    - Truman Hold letters telegrams fo Mc Arthur, 1951
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDANCE file, 1956-1958
    Arr.alphabetically by header/heading in folders enveloppes
    - COMPLIMENTS TO MCDONOUGH (opinion polls), 1958 (Box G C 40)
    - COMPLIMENTS QUESTIONS ASKED, 1958
    - COMMENTS ONLY ON 3/7/58 NEWSLETTER (see folder)
    - MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDNCE (see folder), 1960
    - MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDNCE (see folder), 1961
    - NO TAX ON DIVIDENDS CORRESPONDANCE (double taxations)
    - O GENERAL HR 358 3780 3868 4392, 1957- 1958
      (Federalbudget aid to Education, federal corporate income tax, Hoover commission, pensions of widows of Spanish-American war veterans, Social Security rates, Wilmington oilfield Customs house Federal building in L.A).
    - OPPOSED TO FEDERAL AID TO EDUCATION (School assistence act of '61), 1961
    - P GENERAL HR 6452 8002, 1957-1958
      (Bow resolution, Bricker amendment, Federal budget, Gloria Parker records, income taxes on pensions, Irish sweepstake in U.S., sale of desert land in California by Bureau of Land Management, Tito visit, von Brentano visit)
    - PUBLICATIONS RECEIVED (American Chemical Society, Bank of Hawaii '58 report, Betelem reviews-steel in our highways-, boys clubs of America, Comptroller of US currency, Container Corp. of America, Export-Import Bank of Washington,Federal Housing Administration, L A Chamber of Commerce, L A County Flood Control District) SEE FOLDER, 1956
    - PUBLICATIONS RECEIVED SEE FOLDER, 1959
    - Q GENERAL (Sen. W F Knowland), 1958
    - R GENERAL H J RES 61 355, 1956-1958
      (benefits availabe to vets., Bricker amendment, F B I file opening, House of Un-American activities, income tax reduction, paid T V, Hungarian delegation visit to US, role of US in world affairs) SEE FOLDER
    - S GENERAL HR I 430 2137 S 76 H J RES 4, 1956-1958
      (A H bomb testing,Bricker amendment, Hoover Committee recondadation, loyalty oath for churches tax exempt,repeal 16th amendment, revision of tax program, tax reductions, Tito visit, war against our immigration laws booklet,women's role in machinery of government.
    - T GENERAL HR 2153 6659 HJ 355 S 83, 1956-1958
      (Educational benefits post Korean conflict veterans, Federal budget, civil rights act of '57, pensions for widows from Spanish was 1898, student exchangeplan, tax rates SEE FOLDER
    - U GENERAL H J RES 256, 1957
      (F B I file opening, Federal aid to education, Hoover Commission recondations,L A Customs house Federal office building)
    - V GENERAL HR 8002, 1956-1958
      (civil rights,Federal aid to education, grants in aid,new smog device (Vecchio), Supreme Court)
    - W GENERAL HR 7739 7740 SB 241), 1957-1958
      (ARTICLE; the America we lost, budget cuts, independant oil producers, Public Health Serve.)
    - X Y Z GENERAL HR 3660 H RES 85, 1957-1958
      (Patman resolutionTalle bill)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDANCE FILE, 1956-1958
    Arr. alphabetically by subject headers/heading in folders enveloppes
    - A GENERAL HR 3 2359 DB 584 (Weinberger bill, Norman Adams), 1956-'58 (Box G C 41)
    - B GENERAL HR 4 DB 584 H J RES 4, 1958-'58
    - C GENERAL S 72 (Tales Rhett), 1956-'58
    - D GENERAL HR 1108 7574 AB 2712 (Doyle), 1957-'58
    - E GENERAL HR 1 3986 5797 8027 S 1168 SB 2290, 1956-'58
    - F GENERAL AB 2000 2001, 1957-'58
    - G GENERAL HR 11672 11673, 1957-'58
    - H GENERAL HR 5124 12181 H J RES 355 HR 8002 S 2646 (B D R lamps-Electonic lamps incorporated), 1957-'58
    - I GENERAL, 1957
    - J GENERAL, 1957-'58
    - K GENERAL HR 3 2767 4662 S 337 S J 5 Public Law 569 810 (Bricker amendment, Fedral Aid to Education, Drag motors, Radial meeganics), 1957-'58
    - L GENERAL H J RES 355 (History of North-American Aviation Company), 1957-'58
    - Mc GENERAL HR 4797 HJ RES 256 HR 3208 8278 (Automobile safety device, taxes on personal property within National Parks, legislation pertainig to veterans.), 1957-'58
    - M GENERAL HR 5472 S 1805 Public Law 881 HR 5024 5472 (Annuity increase retired emplpyees, employment in California, survivors benefits, tax credit on retired incomes.), 1956-'58
    - N GENERAL HR 330 1 4575 J RES 4 123 232 HR 12832 S 2646 3778 (Civil Service Commission, Federal Firearms regulating veterans W W I legislative Committee bulletin W W veterans pensions), 1957-'58 1956/57
    - PUBLICATIONS RECEIVED Bookets: Agricultural life camps for migratory workers, decade of growth Pacific Gas Electric Companies, Newsprint-forward look to '65 a.o.) SEE FOLDER, 1957 '57, 1946-[UNK]
    - CORRESPONDANCE SEE FOLDER, 1955-'56
    - CORRESPONDANCE T thr. Z HR 256 2840 36346, 1955-'56
    - FOREIGN AID AGAINST Correspondance
    - MEXICAN-AMERICAN REVIEW issue, 1955
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDANCE file, 1958-1962
    correspondance in folders marked GENERAL A thr Z
    box arr. by folder heading General....
    - GENERAL A, 1959 thr. 1962 (Box G C 42)
    - GENERAL B, 1958 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL C, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL D Sonia Davis, 1960 thr. 1961
    - GENERAL D, 1960 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL E, 1959 thr. 1961
    - GENERAL F, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL G, 1958 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL H, 1958 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL I, 1960 thr. 1961
    - GENERAL J, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL K, 1958 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL L, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL M, 1958 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL Mc, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL N, 1959 thr. 1961
    - GENERAL O, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL P, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL R, 1958 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL S, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL T, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL U, 1961
    - GENERAL V, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL W, 1959 thr. 1962
    - GENERAL X Y Z, 1959 thr. 1962
- File of LEGISLATION introduced/sponsored by Sen MCDONOUGH, 1945-1962
  Box Lists; arranged alphabetically by SUBJECT in folders enveloppesin in boxes 43 through 55
  RELIEF Bills range of bills indicated f.i. HR 1563 thr 1130 number of bill
  Box numbering in time sequence
  - LEGISLATION introduced 80th Congress 2nd Session, 1945/47
    Arr. aphabetically by Subject in Manilla enveloppes
    Horizontal arr.: subject, year(s) of introduction Corr., related bills
    - Agricultural Dept., 1947-48 (Box Box LEGISL. 43)
    - Federal Communication Commission, 1947-48
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1947
    - Forest Service Dept. of Agriculture, 1945
    - Labor Dept. Labor inf. bulletin 1945 Report II National Conference Labor Legislation, 1947-48, '45 '46 1944
    - U S Coast Guard, 1945
    - U S Civil Service Commission, 1945, '46
    - Veterans Organisations,.. letters from 1947, '48
    - War Dept. Enlistement lists, corr., 1945
      - 1947, '46
      - 1947-48
    - War Dept. Cases- Down grading
    - War Dept. Form ans. for officers rec. Reg. Commissions (appontment lists), 1947, '58
    - Economy, 1947
    - BILLS arr. by bill nr.
      Horizontal arr. same in foldersenveloppes Bills period 1950- '58 date underlined
      - Monopoly Power 1951 (report of sub-mommittee on study monopoly power* '5, H RES 95
      - Definition of Communism 1947 H R 2122, 99
        (booklets: Communists within th Government '47 US Chamber of commerce Judgement of God on Russian confederacy Talbot Present distres of nations God's answers Talbot Invasion of Palestine by the northern conferedacy Tabot
      - Cosmetic Tax 1949, '48 H R 4913, H R 204
      - Amend veterans regulations nr I (A) srevice connected tuberculoses, 1953, 52; 310
      - Bill directing secretary of commerce to provide larger allocations of supher to increase production of newsprint 83 Congress 1st session, 1953, '51; 317
      - Construction of L A Postoffice garage H R 331 861 1355 1363 5013, 1957, '54 '55; 1184
      - Case anti-lynching bill, 1947; 3488
      - Hamasaki H R 776 8425 81 Congress 1 session, 1950, '51 '56; 8425
    - Private Bills S 382 381 1051, 1950
    - Secretary of Navy, annual report etc. Presidenr, 1944
  - LEGISLATION introduced by Sen McDounough 80th Congress 2nd Session, 1946/48
    Arr. aphabetical by Subject in folders enveloppes
    Hor. arr.: Subject, year(s) of introduction correspondace, related Bills
    - Civil Service HR 3872 2948 3232, 1947 (Box Box LEGISL 44)
    - Colorado River S D 1175 H J R 226 S J R 145 HR 5901, 1948
    - Federal Credit Union S 2225, 1948
    - Fair Employment practises Bill (FEPC) Hr 2824 S 984, 1947, '48
    - Federal Employee Annuity Tax exemption, 1947
    - Federal Employee Pay raise H R 5067 5472, 1948
    - Federal Housing Adm. (FHA), 1947
    - Federal Lands H B 727, 1947
    - Federal Statues Amendment, 1947
    - Fingerprints, 1947
    - Firearms H R 1061, 1947
    - Fur Tax 47, 1946 '
    - Immigration H R 2910 6396 S 2242, 1948, '46 '47
    - Import Duty, 1948
    - Indian H R 4627, 1948, '47
    - Intelligence Service, 1948
    - Interior Dept., 1947
    - Japanese-American H R 3566 3699[UNK], 1947, '48
    - Labor, 1947
    - Judicial H R 2470 S 941, 1947 '48
    - Labor (Lanbor in California 1946) H R 725 888 S 133 360 858 11 26, 1947 '48
    - Labor conggratulation on vote H R 3020, 1947
    - Labor on the job training, 1947
    - Labor minimum wage, 1948
    - Library S 48 H R 2465, 1947
    - Maritime H R 476 4908, 1947
    - Marshall Plan (report 418 Economic Cooperation ACt), 1948
    - Meat Inspection H R 2256 5675, 1947 '48
    - Meat Public Law 610, 1948
    - Mining H R 1626 2404, 1947 '48
    - Monopoly, 1948
    - National Cemetary, 1947
    - National Defense H R 2744 3227 4090 4231 5733 S 461 1570 4162, 1948, '47
    - National Science Foundation, 1947
    - Panama Canal H R 2273 S 738, 1948, '47
    - Patent H R 6007, 1946, '47 '48
    - Pensions H R 715, 1947
    - Petroleum H R 2185, 1947 '48
    - Philippine, 1947
    - Police Fireman Retirement H R 1613, 1948
    - Postal Rate S B 813, 1948
    - Postal H R 2436 2985 4640 S 1949, 1947, '48
    - Presedential Term, 1947
    - Prohibition S b 265, 1947
    - Public Health H R 5675, 1948
    - Railroad retirement (Railroad retirement act '46 Public Law 572 H R 2169 2310 2911 2853 2854 S 994, 1947
    - Tax H B 3866 1613, 1947, '48
    - Tax income, 1948, '47
    - Territories H R 3309S 1184, 1947
    - Tidelands oil H R 4999 S 1488 (SUPREME COURT DECISION U S versus Calif., 1947 '48
  - Legislation introduced by Sn. McDONOUGH 80th Congress 2nd Session, 1947/48
    Arranged aphabetically by Subject in folders
    Horizontal arr. by subject, year(s) of introduction correspondane, related bills
    - Economy, 1947 (Box Box LEGISL 45)
    - Education House Bill 2953 '48, 1947
    - Election Law, 1947
    - Equal Rights, 1947, '48
    - Equal Rights Amendment Space Session, 1948
    - Export Control H R 3229 '48 S J R 167, 1948, '47
    - Gambling H R 879 '47, 1946, '47
    - General Legislation H R 234 '47, 1947, '46
    - Government Annuity H R 2273 '47, 1947
    - GovernmentControl, 1947 '48
    - Guam, 1947
    - Holds Marshall Plan, 1948, '47
    - Horses H R 3484 '47 H R 2868 '47, 1947
    - Hospital Medical Research, 1946
    - Labor Dept., 1947, '48
    - Labor Portal pay H R 4387 H R6534 S 2788, 1948
    - Labor, 1947
    - Legal Legislation H R 3022 H R 1369 H R 2657, 1947, '46 '48
    - Loan Service Control, 1946
    - Marshall Plam, 1948
    - National Resources Board H R 4051 H R 1330 H R 1974 H R 3866, 1947, '48
    - National Guard H R 3227 H R 2744, 1947
    - Navy Senate Bill 222 H R 1389 S 657, 1947, '48
    - Negro H R 4664 S 1641, 1948
    - Optometry H R 524 H R 6087, 1958
    - Postal Employee's H R3232 H R 3075 S 637 H R 1321 H R 378 H R 2985, 1947, '46
    - Postal Office, 1947
    - Post Employee Pay H R 5667, 1958, '47
    - Peace Plae Mission, 1948
    - Public Accounts H R 5732, 1948
    - Railroad (General) H R 210 H R 1639 H R 3237 S 429, 1947 '48
    - Railroad Howell Bill H R 3150, 1947
    - Railroad Retirement H R 6766 H R 5993 H R 6766, 1948
    - Reclamation Irrigation H R 2873 H R 1977, 1948 '47
    - Recording, 1948
    - Relief (privateDr. Medlin)H R 4787, 1948
    - Relief Chadar Rao H R 4442, 1948
    - Rent Control, 1948 '47
    - Rent Control Hold H R 4662, 1948 '47
    - Reorganization Plan nr 1, 1948
    - Reorganization Plan nr 3, 1947
    - Rubber HR 5314, 1948
    - Special Sessions, General, 1948
    - Silver Price, 1947
    - Social Security H R 80 H J RES 296, 1947, '45 '48
    - Socialized Medicine, 1947'45
    - State Dept., 1947
    - Subsidy H R 2455 House Bill 177 H R 30, 1947
    - Tariff H R 1123, 24 H R 2404, 1947
    - Tariff, 1948 '47
    - Taxation, opposes reduction, 1957 '46
    - Ownsend H R 16, 1947 '48
    - War Assets Administration, 1947
    - Water Pollution H R 147 H R 2455 H R 2494 S 418, 1947 '48
    - War Prisoners H R 4044, 1948
    - War Dept. H R 2744, 1947
    - Wool Bill S 1498 S 814, 1947
    - World Government, 1948
    - World Health Organization, 1948
  - LEGISLATION introduced by Sen McDonough 83 Congress, 1954/55
    - Relief Bills (Box Box LEGISL 46)
      - Tin-yu-Kwong. H R 831, 1951 *; H R 780
      - Statherakos, H R 6296, 1953, '54; 6296
      - Robert J Rickards H R 4818 Private Law 118, 1953, '52; 847
      - Frank.A Wefel, H R 3896 Private Bill 7457, 1953, '50 '51 '52; 850
      - Burnaman, H R 8743 8742, 1955, '54; 1194
      - Stefanos A.Spillios Private Law 89 S 709 1262, 1953, '52; 2192
      - Florace M. Emery, 1953; 4706
      - Yahoubian, 1953; 5290 5291
      - Adjudication of claims to water of Colorado river (pmphlets ao) H R 934 H J RES 3, 55 SJR 4, S 75, 1953, '48 '49 '50; H J RES 54
      - Proposed Central Arizona Project, examiniation reports on..... H J RES 282, 1953 '49 '51; 55
      - Bricker Amendment correspondence H J RES 7, 28[UNK], 57, 325 H J R 167 S J REA 1, 1953-'54; 57
      - Relief Mrs. Coral M.Home H RES 134, 1953; 143
      - Postal Field Service Employees,grade classification salary scale, 1953; 59
      - Inquiry into Government in Business H R 992 4406 15 S 106, 1514, 1953, '54; H RES 102
      - Tidelanda H R 312 860 1364 4484 4999 S 1988 S J RES 20 HR Report 695 Louisiana Res 22, 1953, '51 '48 '49 '50; H R 2726
      - Excise Tax, reduce... Report 1085, 1954; 8224
      - Improvement 'Marina Del Rey inlet Bassin Venice H R 9859 H R Document 389 Public Law 780 AssemblyRes 108, 1954, '55 '56 '57; 7481
      - Marina Del Rey, L A County H R 9859, 1954, '53; 7481
      - Authorise development of Venice-Playa Del Rey Aarea, 1954, '52 '57; 7481
    - Bills introduced by McDoungh 83 Congress (bills listings), 1953/54
    - Bills introduced by McDoungh 83 Congress bills only, 1953
    - In 2 enveloppes Copies of Bills H R J RES 56 57 58 59 102 329 330
  - LEGISLATION introduced by Sen McDonough 84th Congress, 1954-'57
    Arr. alphabetically by Subject in forders enveloppes
    Horitontal arr.: Subject, year(s) of introduction correspondance, related Bills
    - Advertising, 1954 (Box Box LEGISL 47)
    - Agriculture H R 12, 1955, '56
    - Airforce, 1956
    - Alaska Statehood, 1956
    - Anti-Trust, 1956
    - Anti-Vivisection, 1956
    - Army Armed Services H R 554 2187 2188 2213 2215 2607 4383 6408, 1954
      - 6817 7565 8409, '55
      - S 106 1634 1643 2086 6143, '56
    - Atlantic Treaty, 1954
    - Aviation H R 6260 7922 8000, 1955, '56
    - Banking S 1188 256 1736, 1956
    - Bank ruptcy, 1955
    - Labor H R 7335 S 1644, 1954, '55 '56
    - L A Smog problem (clean air for California booklet), 1954
    - L A Smog legislation (reprts, studies correspondance), 1955-'57
    - N legislation file H R 6904, 1955
    - P legislation file H R 4267 4627 4943 6645 6346 4983 S 1853, 1955, '56
    - M legislation file H R100 595 3126 3315 3381 4230 4374 5221 5561 S 2090, 1955
    - Appropriations, 1955
    - Colorado River (matrial on Upper Basin legisl.), 1955
    - Economy, 1955
    - Federal Judge, 1956
    - Postal Pay H R 1592 1955 2117 4644
    - Postal Employee, 1956
    - BILLS intr. 84th Congress
      NOT re-introduced 85th Congress
      Same arrangement
      - Retirement privileges post office guards HR 8589, 1955, '54; HR 337
      - Permit rental of housing for period of under 30 days, 1955, '54; 1588
      - Smog research by HEW H R 835 5860 S 928, 1955; 3680
      - L A Harbor Amendment H R 4734 9859 Public Law 780, 1955, '53; 4683
      - Purchase of site for new L A Federal Building Public Law 519, 1955, '56 '57; 4685
      - Correct Pay day postal employees, 1956; 5808
      - Tax deduction for private schools H R 2838, 1956, '55; 6438
      - Fisheries H R 8001, 1956; 8378
  - LEGISLATION introduced by Sen. McDonough 85th Congress, 1957/1958
    Arr. aphabetically by Subject
    Horizontal arr.: Subject, year(s) of introduction correspondance, related bills
    - Agriculture H R 7760 9020 11793, 1955-1958 (Box Box LEGISL 48)
    - Airforce, 1957
    - Alaska Statehood, 1957, '58
    - Animal Trapping H R 9303 S 2489, 1957
    - Anti Trust H R 264 2143 S 198 S 722, 1957
    - Army Armed Services H R 7574 7642 9979 11470 S 1085 S 1994 2014 H R 689, 1953-1988
    - Aviation H R 12616, 1957,58
    - Atomic energy atomic Bomb, 1957
    - Banking, 1957
    - Budget, 1957
    - Colorado River, 1957
    - Commerce, 1957
    - Commerce H R 3233 S 939, 1957
    - Central Valley H R 6035 9969 11899, 1958
    - Civil Defence S 1887, 1957
    - Civil Rights H R 6127, 1956 *
    - Civil Service, 1957
    - Customs H R 4120 5098 5378, 1957
    - Defence H R 12541, 1958
    - District of Columbia H R 6763, 1957
    - Federal Pay Raise S 734, 1958
    - Food Drug H R 6814, 1957
    - Foreign Aid, 1957, '58
    - Foreign Policy, 1957
    - Foreign Trade H R 8382, 1958
    - General Services Adm. (G S A) H R 1535 5695, 1958
    - Handicapped Aid H R 8609 S 2411[UNK], 1957
    - Hawaii Statehood, 1958
    - Immigration H R3787 7675 S 866 S 2248, 1957
    - Kenny-Ives S 3974, 1958
    - Legal H R 3349 3350 7006 S932, 1957
    - L A Flood Control H R 41921 S 4971, 1958
    - L A Harbour Improvement, 1955-'58
    - Mental Health H CON RES 98 SN 245, 1957,'58
    - Merchant Marine H R 6709 11078 11415, 1957,'58
    - Mining, 1957
    - National Anthem, 1948
    - National Freedom Board, 1957 '58
    - National Guard, 1957
    - National Resources, 1958;'57
    - Patent H R 103, 1957
    - Petroleum, 1957
    - Postal Legisl., 1957, '58
    - Post Office Appropr., 1957
    - Post Office, 1957, '58
    - Postal Rate Service H R5836, 1957 '58
    - Private Bill, 1957
    - Public Works S 555 S 3497, 1957
    - Pure Food H R 7798 9521, 1958
    - Railroad Retirement H R 3665 4553 5551, 1958,'57
    - Rail Road H R 12488 S 3778 SR 3031, 1957, '58
    - Sports H R 10378 12990 12993, 1958
    - Seawater conversion H R 11405, 1958
    - Gold Star Mothers, 1957
    - Highway, 1957,'58
    - Organisation Charter H R 388 1138, 1957
    - Housing, 1957 '58
    - Judicial, 1958
    - Passports, 1958